QUESTIONS = [
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "What is the capital of Norway?",
        "choices": {
            "A": "Bergen",
            "B": "Oslo",
            "C": "Stavanger",
            "D": "Trondheim"
        },
        "answer": "B"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "What is the currency of Norway?",
        "choices": {
            "A": "Euro",
            "B": "Pound",
            "C": "Krone",
            "D": "Deutsche Mark"
        },
        "answer": "C"
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "What is the largest city in Norway?",
        "choices": {
            "A": "Oslo",
            "B": "Stavanger",
            "C": "Bergen",
            "D": "Trondheim"
        },
        "answer": "A"
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "When is Constitution Day (the national day) of Norway?",
        "choices": {
            "A": "27th May",
            "B": "17th May",
            "C": "17th April",
            "D": "27th April"
        },
        "answer": "B"
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "What color is the background of the Norwegian flag?",
        "choices": {
            "A": "Red",
            "B": "White",
            "C": "Blue",
            "D": "Yellow"
        },
        "answer": "A"
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "How many countries does Norway border?",
        "choices": {
            "A": "1",
            "B": "2",
            "C": "3",
            "D": "4"
        },
        "answer": "C"
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "What is the name of the university in Trondheim?",
        "choices": {
            "A": "UiS",
            "B": "UiO",
            "C": "NMBU",
            "D": "NTNU"
        },
        "answer": "D"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "How long is the border between Norway and Russia?",
        "choices": {
            "A": "96 km",
            "B": "196 km",
            "C": "296 km",
            "D": "396 km"
        },
        "answer": "B"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "Where in Norway is Stavanger?",
        "choices": {
            "A": "North",
            "B": "South",
            "C": "South-west",
            "D": "South-east"
        },
        "answer": "C"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "From which Norwegian city did the world's famous composer Edvard Grieg come?",
        "choices": {
            "A": "Oslo",
            "B": "Bergen",
            "C": "Stavanger",
            "D": "Troms√∏"
        },
        "answer": "B"
    }
]
